Guide to the Architectural Drawings and Maps of Yale University Buildings and Grounds
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale Architectural drawings and maps (microfilmed), circa 1880-1980; Series I
  - 2:33 British Art Center
    - first project - preliminary drawings (Box 26B)
    - first project - preliminary drawings (Box 27A)
    - first project - preliminary drawings (Box 27B)
    - first project - preliminary drawings (Box 27C)
    - first project - preliminary drawings (Folder 28)
    - Louis Kahn originals (Folder 29)
    - first project - sketches (Box 30)
    - first project - preliminary drawings (Box 31)
    - second project - sketches (Box 30)
    - second project - preliminary drawings (Box 33A)
    - second project - preliminary drawings (Box 33B)
    - third project - sketches (Folder 34)
    - third project - sketches (Box 35)
    - third project - sketches (Box 36A)
    - third project - sketches (Box 36B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Folder 37)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Folder 38)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Folder 39)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 40)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 41A)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 41B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 42A)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 42B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 43A)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 43B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 44)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 45A)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 45B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 46A)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 46B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 46C)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 47A)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 47B)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 47C)
    - third project - preliminary drawings (Box 47D)
    - third project - working drawings (Box 48A)
    - third project - working drawings (Box 48B)
    - third project - working drawings (Box 48C)
    - third project - working drawings (Box 49A)
    - third project - working drawings (Box 49B)
  - 3:02 University Club (Folder 50)
  - 3:03 242 York Street (Garland Apartments) (Folder 51)
  - 3:07 University Theatre (222 York St) (Folder 52)
  - 3:25 Pierson/Davenport Colleges
    - Drawings (Folder 53–64, Folder 67)
    - Program and feasibility study, 2001 December 12 (Box 741)
    - Vol. I Program Development, 2001 December 12 (Box 741)
    - Vol. II Scope, 2001 December 12 (Box 741)
    - Vol. III Appendix, 2001 December 12 (Box 741)
    - Vol. IV building systems diagrams, 2001 December 12 (Box 741)
  - 3:26 Briton Hadden Memorial Building (Folder 65)
  - 3:32 Beta Theta Pi (Folder 66)
  - 3:36 254 York Street (Folder 67)
  - 3:43 Art and Architecture Building (182 York St) (Folder 68–69)
  - 3:60 Zeta Psi (212 York St) (Folder 70)
  - 3:61 Delta Kappa Epsilon (232 York) (Folder 71)
  - 3:63 Fence Club (Psi Epsilon) (Folder 72)
  - 3:63 Fence Club (Psi Epsilon) (Folder 73)
  - 4:03 Peabody Museum (Folder 74)
  - 4:04 Sloane Physical Laboratory (Folder 75)
  - 4:11 Boiler House and Steam Department (Folder 76)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Folder 77)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 77A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 77B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 77C)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 77D)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Folder 78)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Folder 79)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 79A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 79B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 80A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 80B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 80C)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 80D)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 80E)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Folder 81)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 81A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 81B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 81C)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Folder 82)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 82A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 82B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 82C)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 82D)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 83A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 83B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 84A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 84B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 84C)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 84D)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 85A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 85B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 86A)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 86B)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 86C)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Box 87)
  - 4:29 Weir Hall (66 High St) (Box 87)
  - 4:34 Jonathan Edwards College (68 High St)
    - preliminary presentation drawings, plans, elevations, sections (Folder 88)
    - Details (Folder 89)
    - Details (Folder 90)
    - Details (Folder 92)
    - Details (Folder 93)
    - Details (Folder 94)
    - Details (Folder 95)
    - Details (Folder 96)
    - drawings (Folder 91)
  - 4:37 Art Gallery (1111 Chapel St)
    - blueprints (Folder 97)
    - blueprints (Folder 98)
    - proposed addition (Folder 99)
    - blueprints - floor plans (Folder 100)
    - drawings - floor plans (Folder 101)
    - drawings (Folder 102)
    - drawings (Folder 102A)
  - 5:10 Hall of Graduate Studies (320 York St)
    - drawings (Folder 103)
    - design drawings (Folder 104)
    - design drawings (Box 104A)
    - Working drawings (Folder 105)
    - working drawings (Box 105A)
    - working drawings (Box 105B)
    - elevations and sections (Box 106)
    - drawings (Folder 107)
    - working drawings - details (Folder 108)
    - details (Folder 109)
    - details (Folder 110)
    - Details (Folder 111)
    - details (Box 111A)
    - details (Box 111B)
    - details (Box 111C)
    - details (Folder 112)
    - details (Folder 113)
    - details (Folder 114)
    - details (Folder 115)
  - 5:16, 5:17 Morse and Stiles Colleges (Box 116A)
  - 5:16, 5:17 Morse and Stiles Colleges (Folder 116B)
  - 5:18 Yale Co-Operative Corporation (Box 117A)
  - 5:18 Yale Co-Operative Corporation (Box 117B)
  - 6:16 Payne-Whitney Gymnasium (70 Tower Pkwy) (Folder 118)
  - 7:04 University Gymnasium (Folder 119)
  - 7:05 Carnegie Swimming Pool (Folder 120)
  - 7:10 Psi Upsilon Tomb (Folder 121)
  - 7:30 Zeta Psi (Box 35)
  - 7:31 Sterling Memorial Library (120 High St)
    - Preliminaries: Goodhue schemes plus Rogers schemes E, F, G, I, K, M, O, P, Q and Q (R) (Folder 123)
    - Preliminary "Schemes" (Folder 124)
    - Preliminary "Schemes" (Folder 124A)
    - Final Building Design: Preliminaries (Folder 125)
    - Presentation Plans (Folder 126–127)
    - Working Plans (Folder 128)
    - Working Plans (Folder 129)
    - Working Elevations (Folder 130)
    - Working Elevations (Folder 131)
    - Working Elevations (Folder 132)
    - Working Elevations (Folder 133)
    - Working Sections (Folder 134)
    - Working Details (Folder 135)
    - Working Details (Folder 136)
    - Working Details (Folder 137)
    - Working Details (Folder 138)
    - Working Details (Folder 139)
    - Working Details (Folder 140)
    - Working Details (Folder 141)
    - Working Details (Folder 142)
    - Working Details (Folder 143)
    - Working Details (Folder 144)
    - Working Details (Folder 145)
    - Working Details (Folder 146)
    - Working Details (Folder 147)
    - Working Details: Shop Drawings and Schedules (Folder 148)
    - 126 High Street Addition (Rare Book Room--Currently Manuscripts and Archives): Presentation Drawings, Working Drawings: Plan, Sections and Elevations (Folder 149)
    - 126 High Street Addition (Rare Book Room--Currently Manuscripts and Archives): Working Drawings: Details (Folder 150)
    - Post-Rogers Additions and Alterations: Working Drawings (Folder 151A)
    - Post-Rogers Additions and Alterations: Working Drawings (Folder 151B)
    - Post-Rogers Additions and Alterations: Cross Campus and Light Court, Sterling Annex (Folder 152A)
    - Post-Rogers Additions and Alterations: Cross Campus and Light Court, Sterling Annex (Folder 152B)
    - Post-Rogers Additions and Alterations: Cross Campus and Light Court, Sterling Annex (Folder 152C)
    - Post-Rogers Additions and Alterations: Cross Campus and Light Court, Sterling Annex (Box 35)
  - 7:35 245-247 Elm (Folder 153)
  - 7:36 Trumbull
    - 1929-1933 (Folder 154)
    - Working Drawings: Details (Folder 155–159)
    - Working Drawings: Details (Folder 156)
    - Working Drawings: Details (Folder 157)
    - Working Drawings: Details (Folder 158)
    - Working Drawings: Details (Folder 159)
  - 8:01 Hopkins Grammar School (Box 35)
  - 8:16 Sterling Law Buildings (127 Wall St)
    - Elevations, Plans, Sections (Folder 161)
    - Drawing #'s 1-99 (Folder 162)
    - Drawing #'s 200s, 300-349 (Folder 163)
    - Drawing #'s 350-399 (Folder 164)
    - Drawing #'s 400-449 (Folder 165)
    - Drawing #'s 450-499 (Folder 166)
    - Drawing #'s 500-549 (Folder 167)
    - Drawing #'s 550-599 (Folder 168)
    - Drawing #'s 4000-4049 (Folder 169)
    - Drawing #'s 4050-4099 (Folder 170)
    - Drawings (Folder 171)
    - Drawing #'s 4100-4149 (Folder 172)
    - Drawing #'s 4150-4199 (Folder 173)
  - 9:02 East Divinity (Folder 174)
  - 9:15 President's House (126 College) (Folder 175)
  - 9:16 Fayerweather Hall (Folder 176)
  - 9:20 Haughton Hall (Folder 177)
  - 9:23 Porter Gateway (Folder 178)
  - 9:24 Sprague Hall (Folder 179)
  - 9:26 120 College (Folder 180)
  - 9:33 William L. Harkness Hall (100 Wall St) (Box 309)
  - 9:34 Calhoun College (189 Elm St) (Box 182)
  - 9:34 Calhoun College (189 Elm St) (Box 35)
  - 9:35 Berkeley College (205 Elm St) (Folder 183)
  - 9:35 Berkeley College (205 Elm St) (Folder 184)
  - 9:35 Berkeley College (205 Elm St) (Folder 185)
  - 9:35 Berkeley College (205 Elm St) (Folder 186)
  - 9:36 Cross Campus Library (120 High St) (Box 187)
  - 9:36 Cross Campus Library (120 High St) (Box 188A)
  - 9:36 Cross Campus Library (120 High St) (Box 188B)
  - 10:13 Bicentennial Buildings (Folder 189)
  - 10:13 Bicentennial Buildings: Hewitt Quadrangle (Folder 190)
  - 10:13 Bicentennial Buildings: Proposed Administration Building (Folder 191)
  - 10:13 Bicentennial Buildings: Proposed Administration Building (Folder 192)
  - 10:18 Woodbridge Hall (105 Wall St) (Folder 193)
  - 10:18 Woodbridge Hall (105 Wall St) (Folder 194)
  - 10:24 Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
    - Drawings (Folder 195A)
    - Drawings (Box 195B)
    - Drawings (Box 196)
    - Drawings (Box 197A)
    - Drawings (Box 197B)
    - Drawings (Box 198)
    - Drawings (Box 199)
    - Drawings (Box 200)
    - Design Drawings (Box 309)
    - Drawings (Folder 202)
    - Design Drawings (Folder 203)
    - Drawings (Box 204A)
    - Drawings (Box 204B)
    - Drawings (Box 205A)
    - Drawings (Box 205B)
    - Design Drawings (Box 206)
  - 10:24 Sterling Memorial Annex (Box 207A)
  - 10:24 Sterling Memorial Annex (Box 207B)
  - 11:03 Hendrie Hall (165 Elm St) (Box 309)
  - 11:06 Elizabethan Club (123 College) (Folder 209)
  - 11:07 74-78 Wall (Folder 210)
  - 11:18 325-327 Temple (Folder 211)
  - 11:19 Stoeckel Hall (96 Wall St) (Box 212)
  - 12:07 Byers Hall (Box 309)
  - 12:11 Vanderbilt Scientific (Box 214)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St) (Folder 215)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St) (Folder 216)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St) (Folder 217)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St) (Folder 218)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St) (Folder 219)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St) (Folder 220)
  - 12:28 Silliman College (505 College St) (Folder 221)
  - 12:29 St. Anthony Hall (Folder 222)
  - 13:01 South Sheffield (Folder 223)
  - 13:02 North Sheffield (Box 309)
  - 13:05 Winchester (Folder 225)
  - 13:16 Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall (1 Prospect St) (Folder 226)
  - 13:18 Becton Engineering Center (15 Prospect St) (Folder 227A)
  - 13:18 Becton Engineering Center (15 Prospect St) (Box 227B)
  - 14:04 Mason Lab (Folder 228)
  - 14:10 Berzelius (Box 229)
  - 14:11 1 Hillhouse (Folder 230)
  - 14:15 370 Temple (Folder 231)
  - 14:22 St. Elmo (Folder 232)
  - 15:02 Hammond Lab (Folder 233)
  - 16:06 89 Trumbull (Box 234)
  - 16:08 111 Prospect (Folder 235)
  - 16:10 135 Prospect (Box 236)
  - 16:11 Watson Building (60 Sachem St) (Folder 237)
  - 17:9 President's House (43 Hillhouse Ave) (Folder 238)
  - 18:04 155 Whitney (Folder 239)
  - 19:02 Marsh Hall (360 Prospect) (Folder 240)
  - 19:07 Irving Fisher House (460 Prospect St) (Folder 241)
  - 19:19 Greeley Memorial Laboratory (370 Prospect St)
    - Preliminaries and Early Plans, 1957 (Folder 242)
    - Blueprints, 1959 (Folder 243)
  - 19:25 218 Prospect (Folder 244)
  - 20:01 Sloane Physics Laboratory (Folder 245)
  - 20:01 Sloane Physics Laboratory (Box 245B)
  - 20:02 Osborn Memorial Labratory (165 Prospect St) (Folder 246)
  - 20:03 Pierson-Sage Boiler and Refrigeration Plant (Folder 247)
  - 20:05 Sterling Chemistry Laboratory (225 Prospect St) (Folder 248)
  - 20:06 Peabody Museum of Natural History (170 Whitney Ave) (Folder 249)
  - 20:06 Peabody Museum: Bingham Laboratory Addition (Box 250)
  - 20:07 Sage Hall (205 Prospect St): Bowers Hall Addition (Folder 251)
  - 20:11 Sachem's Wood (Folder 252)
  - 20:13 Accelerator Laboratories (Box 253)
  - 20:14 Gibbs Laboratory
    - Presentation and Architectural Drawings (Box 254A)
    - Presentation and Architectural Drawings (Box 254B)
    - Equipment, Electrical and Plumbing Drawings (Box 255)
  - 20:19, 20:20, 20:23 Kline Geology, Kline Chemistry, Kline Biology (Box 256)
  - 21:01 Winchester Observatory (485 Prospect) (Folder 258)
  - 21:04 Heliostat (Box 259)
  - 21:06 Yale Divinity (Folder 260)
  - 22:01 North Ward (Folder 261)
  - 22:07 Farnam Operating Amphitheatre (Folder 262)
  - 22:22 Jane Ellen Hope Building (315 Cedar St) (Box 263)
  - 22:24 Howard Building (Isolation Pavilion) (Folder 264)
  - 22:29 Nathan Smith Hall (Folder 265)
  - 22:46 William Wirt Winchester (Private Patient Pavilion) (Folder 266)
  - 22:50 Sterling Hall of Medicine (333 Cedar St)
    - General (Folder 267)
    - Institute of Human Relations Addition (Box 268A)
    - Institute of Human Relations Addition (Folder 268B)
    - Medical Library Addition (Folder 269)
  - 22:51 Sterling Power Plant (309 Congress Ave) (Folder 270)
  - 22:67 Farnam Memorial Building (310 Cedar St) (Box 271)
  - 22:68 Lauder Hall (310 Cedar St) (Box 272)
  - 22:68 Lauder Hall (310 Cedar St) (Box 35)
  - 22:99 Raleigh Fitkin (Folder 273)
  - 22:134 Sarah Wey Tompkins Memorial Pavilion (Folder 274)
  - 22:167 Laboratory of Epidemiology and Public Health (Box 309)
  - 22:168 Laboratory of Clinical Investigation (Box 309)
  - 22:189 No. 1 South Street (Box 277)
  - 23:02 Southern Observing Station, Australia (Box 278)
  - 23:03 Bethany Observing Station (Box 278)
  - 23:04 Yale-Columbia Observatory, Argentina (Box 280)
  - 25:01 Yale Field (Folder 281)
  - 25:02 Yale Bowl (Folder 282)
  - 25:03 Yale Armory (Box 35)
  - 25:04 Yale Golf Course (Box 35)
  - 25:05 Lapham Field House (Box 285)
  - 25:05 Lapham Field House (Box 309)
  - 25:06 Walter Camp Field (Box 285)
  - 26:02 Yale Boat House (Box 309)
  - 26:03 Gales Ferry Boat House (Folder 288)
  - 26:04 Adee Boat House (Folder 289)
  - 26:05 Bob Cook Boat House (Folder 290)
  - 27:05 Old William Wirt Winchester Hospital (Box 291)
  - 27:12 Amity Animal Research Facility (Folder 292)
  - 27:24 and 27:25 Lewis Walpole Library and House (Folder 293)
  - 28:15 Hsiang-Ya Hospital
    - Original Designs, Building Details (Folder 294)
    - Preliminaries, Wilson's On-site Designs, Blueprints as done (Folder 295)
  - 90:10-80 Proposals, 1868-1929 (Folder 296)
  - 90:83 Pelton Plan for Medical School (Folder 297)
  - 90:90 Ward Unit A (Folder 298)
  - 90:100 Proposed Women's Dormitory
    - General (Folder 299)
    - Electrical, Structural and Heating Drawings (Folder 300)
    - Electrical and Heating Preliminaries (Box 301)
  - 90:110 Engineering Building (Box 302A)
  - 90:110 Engineering Building (Folder 302B)
  - 90:120 Yale Middle School Reconstruction
  - 90:128-170 Proposals, 1950-1961 (Folder 303)
  - 92:02 Unidentified (Folder 304)
  - 95:87 Map of Yale, undated (Folder 305)
  - 95:5-162 Maps of Yale Property, 1836-1917 (Folder 306A)
  - 95:5-162 Maps of Yale Property, 1836-1917 (Folder 306B)
  - 95:248-420 Maps of Yale Property, 1918-[1980?] (Folder 307)
  - 98:1-2 Thesis Projects (Folder 308)
- Architectural drawings and maps (not microfilmed), Series II
  The materials are open for research.
  In accordance with the donor agreement, access to the Kingsley Trust Association building drawings (boxes 667-671) requires the approval of the current president or treasurer of the Association.
  Contains architectural drawings which have come to the archives after the microfilming project was completed.
  Arranged by region/chronology code.
  - 1:02 Connecticut Hall (344 College St): restoration (11 drawings), undated (Box 310)
  - 1:17 Dwight Hall (67 High St): restoration of old library (12 drawings), undated (Folder 311)
  - 1:20 Street Hall
    - Basement, circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Plan of turrets (2 drawings), circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Main floor, circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Second floor, circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Third floor, circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Drawings (ink on linen), circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Basement plan, circa 1909 (Box 678)
    - Longitudinal section at A.B. (plan 2), 1909 March (Box 678)
    - Foundation at basement plan, 1909 March (Box 678)
    - First story plan, 1909 March 3 (Box 678)
    - Jarves Gallery [section] (Box 678)
    - Jarves Gallery floor plan and section (Box 678)
    - Second story, 1909 March (Box 678)
    - Renderings (Box 678)
    - Sketches (Box 678)
    - First floor (2 drawings) (Box 678)
    - Second floor (Box 678)
    - Alterations (47 drawings), undated (Box 312)
    - Proposed Street Hall remodeling (library) (3 drawings), 1959 (Folder 832)
    - Proposed alterations, Carleton Granbery, architect, 1962 November 21 (Box 624)
  - 1:23 Farnam Hall (380 College St)
    - Floor plans (11 drawings), 1874 (Folder 593)
    - Alteration Plans, Details, 1937 April 5 (Folder 633)
    - Alterations (7 drawings), undated (Box 314)
  - 1:24 Durfee Hall (198 Elm St): alterations (33 drawings), undated (Folder 315)
  - 1:24 Durfee Hall (198 Elm St): alterations (33 drawings), undated (Folder 316)
  - 1:25 Battell Chapel (4 drawings), undated (Box 310)
  - 1:29 Lawrance Hall (358 College St): alterations (5 drawings), undated (Folder 318)
  - 1:30 Linsly Chittenden (63 High St)
    - Chittenden Library (also known as Dwight Hall Chapel), 18 drawings [see oversize], undated (Folder 319)
    - Chittenden Library (also known as Dwight Hall Chapel), 18 drawings [see oversize], undated (Folder 320)
    - 1st floor heating plan, circa 1880s (Folder 594)
    - Comprehensive Renovation
      - GMP Package - site, architectural (Box 743)
      - GMP Package - site, architectural (Box 744)
      - Goody Clancy, 1996 March 15 (Box 743)
      - Goody Clancy, 1996 March 15 (Box 744)
      - Prints (Box 743)
      - Prints (Box 744)
  - 1:32 Welch Hall (330 College St)
    - Alterations (6 drawings), undated (Box 314)
    - Bedroom furniture layout, scheme A (blueprint); Douglas Orr, architect, 1938 April 14 (Folder 628)
  - 1:33 Vanderbilt Hall (1035 Chapel St)
    - 6 drawings, undated (Box 310)
    - One-half of second floor plan: maximum occupancy furniture layout, undated (Folder 628)
    - Plan, 1955 August 9 (Folder 630)
  - 1:33/1:44 Gateway between Bingham and Vanderbilt, 1925 (Folder 598)
  - 1:35 Phelps Hall (344 College St): heating system details (1 drawing), undated (Box 314)
  - 1:39 Linsly Hall (63 High St): Alterations (3 drawings), undated (Folder 324)
  - 1:40 Wright Hall
    - Remodelling basement for post office and Southern New England Telephone Company (SNETCO) (10 drawings), undated (Box 314)
    - Elevations (4 drawings), undated (Folder 595)
    - Floor plans (7 drawings), undated (Folder 596)
    - Details (3 drawings), undated (Folder 597)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall: originals (36 drawings), undated (Folder 326)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall: originals (36 drawings), undated (Folder 327)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall: originals (36 drawings), undated (Folder 328)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall: originals (36 drawings), undated (Folder 329)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall: originals (36 drawings), undated (Folder 330)
  - 1: Old Campus, Durfee Floor Plans (8), Farnam Floor Plans (6), Lawrance Floor Plans (9), McClellan Floor Plans (5), Phelps Floor Plans (5), Bingham Floor Plans (4), Connecticut Hall Floor Plans (9), Welch Floor Plans (10), 1975 July (Folder 633)
  - 1: McClellan Hall details of windows, doors, stonework and cornice (3), 1924 (Box 911)
  - 2:11 Yale Hope Mission (305 Crown St), details (4 drawings), undated (Box 331)
  - 2:13 301 Crown St.: air conditioning (1 drawing), undated (Box 331)
  - 2:15 Yale Press; Carleton Granbery (3 floor plans), 1960 (Box 574)
  - 2:15 1082-1090 Chapel St
    - 1082 Chapel St.
      - 2nd Floor Plan, 1969 July 8 (Folder 634)
      - 3rd Floor Plan, 1969 July 8 (Folder 634)
    - 1084 Chapel St
      - 1st Floor Plan, 1969 July 10 (Folder 634)
      - Plan of interior alterations and repairs, two sheets, 1968 July 18 (Folder 634)
    - 1086 Chapel St.
      - 1st Floor Plan As Is, 1965 August 5 (Folder 634)
      - 2nd and 3rd Floor Plans for proposed alterations, 1969 August 14 (Folder 634)
      - Basement Floor Plan for proposed alterations, 1969 August 14 (Folder 634)
      - 1st Floor Plan for proposed alterations, 1969 August 14 (Folder 634)
      - Drafting Board Units, 1969 September 15 (Folder 634)
      - Dark Room, 1969 September 16 (Folder 634)
      - Basement Floor Plan for proposed alterations, 1969 August 21 (Folder 634)
    - 1088 Chapel St., 1st Floor Plan, 1969 July 9 (Folder 634)
  - 2:19 1094-1106 Chapel St
    - 1104 Chapel St
      - 1st Floor plan, 1969 July 11 (Folder 634)
      - 1104 Chapel St., 1st Floor Plan, 1970 June 19 (Folder 634)
    - 1106 Chapel St
      - Floor Plan and Elevations, 1968 December 20 (Folder 634)
      - 1st Floor and Basement plan, 1969 July 8 (Folder 634)
  - 2:33 British Art Center
    - details (1 drawing), undated (Box 331)
    - Drawings (Box 769)
    - 6 drawings, 1970-1972 (Folder 832)
    - Mechanicals As-Builts, 1973 (Box 782)
    - Sheet Metal, 1973-1974 (Box 784)
    - Sheet Metal, 1973-1974 (Box 786)
    - Architectural Drawings, 1973-1975 (Box 788)
    - Architectural Drawings, 1973-1975 (Box 790)
    - Shop Drawings, 1973-1976 (Box 791)
    - Shop Drawings, 1973-1976 (Box 793)
    - Corrected Mechanicals As-Builts, 1974 (Box 795)
    - Marble, 1974 (Box 808)
    - Drawings, 1974-1975 (Box 797)
    - Shop Drawings, 1974-1975 (Box 799)
  - 2: Schools of Art and Drama (353 Crown and 1156 Chapel) - Superseded Construction Documents
    - Volume 1 (122 drawings), 1999 March (Box 683)
    - Volume 1 (122 drawings), 1999 March (Box 684)
    - Volume 1 (122 drawings), 1999 March (Box 685)
    - Volume 1 (122 drawings), 1999 March (Box 686)
    - Volume 2 (258 drawings), 1999 March (Box 704)
    - Volume 2 (258 drawings), 1999 March (Box 705)
    - Volume 2 (258 drawings), 1999 March (Box 706)
    - Volume 2 (258 drawings), 1999 March (Box 707)
    - Volume 2 (258 drawings), 1999 March (Box 708)
    - Volume 2 (258 drawings), 1999 March (Box 709)
  - 2: 1076 Chapel St., 1st Floor Plan, 1969 July 11 (Folder 634)
  - 2: 1078 Chapel St
    - 1st Floor Plan, 1969 July 11, undated (Folder 634)
    - 2nd, 3rd, and 4th Floors, undated (Folder 634)
  - 2: Chapel 1156 Renovation
    - Existing and proposed, Deborah Berke, 1997 August (Folder 733)
    - Existing and proposed, Deborah Berke, 1997 August (Folder 734)